<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="music_club_description">
        <![CDATA[
        	<h2>Music, IIT Indore</h2>
						</header>
						<p>We will update soon..</p>

						<h3>Follow Music club on facebook click here:
						 <a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/" style="color:blue;">Music Club IITI</a></h3>


        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="photography_club_description">
        <![CDATA[
<h2>Photography Club, IITI</h2>
						</header>
						<p>Photography is an art of observation. It has little to do with the things you see and everything to do with the way you see them. The photography club IIT Indore(Mystic Hues) recognises and nurtures the artist within those geeky minds. The club is renowned as the most active club of IIT Indore and is active throughout the year, and adding on to that we keep on innovating some new ways and ideas within the club to keep it alive.</p>
						<center><p>"You can definitely get the best out of good,photography is when you get the best out of worst"</p></center>

						<h3>Follow Photography club on facebook click here:
						 <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Mystic-Hues-1460698627541295/" style="color:blue;">Mystic-Hues</a></h3>

        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="literary_club_description">
        <![CDATA[
         <h2>The Literary Club, IIT Indore</h2>
						</header>
						<p>Since its inception in 2010, the Literary Club of IIT Indore has always strived to develop an environment where literary excellence is both fostered and developed. With an initial focus on establishing a tradition that purports to the burgeoning urge to express—to express yourself with whatever assistance an imperfect dialect provides‐‐ the club has finally recognised the futility of this arduous task. But, well, it’s still fun.</p>
						<p>Over the years, the club has also expanded by venturing into avenues featuring rhetoric (Monthly Debates)and journalism (Newsletter). IIT-I’s monthly newsletter ‘IMPRINT’, started in October 2014,is the recognition of journalism as a literary praxis. From covering college events to global issues,IMPRINT aims to provide fresh perspectives and developments in every edition.Along with the annual magazine ‘INSCRIPTION’, these two publications often keep the club busy all year.</p>

						<h3>Follow Literary club on facebook click here:
						<a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/literaryiiti" style="color:blue;">literaryiiti</a></h3>


        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="dance_club_description">
        <![CDATA[
          		<h2>Dance Club, IITI</h2>
						</header>
						<p>We will upload soon..</p>
						<h3>Follow Dance club on facebook click here:
						 <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Mystic-Hues-1460698627541295/" style="color:blue;">Mystic-Hues</a></h3>

        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="quiz_club_description">
        <![CDATA[
        <h2>Quiz Club, IIT Indore</h2>
						</header>
						<p>The quiz club is one of the youngest, and most prolific clubs of iit indore,
						 founded in december 2013 with a handful of members. Since then, it has grown into a
						  full fledged community of quizzing enthusiasts, dedicated to serve not just the institute,
						  but students from all over indore, with Quality quizzing experience.</p>
						<h3>Following quizzes have been a part of the club\'s activity calendar:</h3>
						<ul>
							<li><i>Cognitio</i> ­ the annual indore­wide general quiz that sees a renowned Quizmaster
							 as the host, and a handsome cash prize.</li>
							<li><i>MQuizooka</i> ­ the campus general quiz, which pits the best quizzers in a q&a Battle with questions from all the possible genres.</li>
							<li><i>Colosseum </i>­ a public favorite, colosseum presents sports and Entertainment quiz
							 for the dilettante and the initiated alike.</li>
							<li><i>Technophilia</i> ­ as the name suggests, the love for technology fuels the Popularity this quiz has among tech geeks.</li>
							<li><i>Enigma</i> ­ an online quiz the resurges during the fest season, enigma Appeals to quizzers with a thing for puzzles and wild goose chases, and Not to mention, easy money.</li>
							<li><i>Obscura</i> ­ riddles, riddles and riddles; no prerequisites, no newspaper Pursuit required for emerging the victor in this iq quiz.</li>
						<br><br><p>Among other events , we have bollywood quiz, lukkha quizzes, and the Newbie quiz, making special appearances on demand,with much Appreciation received from the audiences.</p>

        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="dramatics_club_description">
        <![CDATA[
          <h2>Abhivyakti-The Dramatics Club, IITI</h2>
						</header>
						<p>The dramatics club of IIT Indore, has been working for the interest of students enthusiastic for acting and stage skills. The club has grown together with the institute and has earned its place inside and outside the campus. Rejuvenated in 2012, the club has participated in a number of competitions like Fluxus, Antaragni, IIT vs IIM and many more. This year, the club gets its name – Abhivyakti. As the name means expression, we endeavor to provide opportunities to explore ones acting skills to the best. One who is extraordinary, gets extraordinary opportunities here. Celebrate expressions!</p>

						<h3 style="font-size:2em;">Events</h3>
						<ul>
						<li>Kesariya</li>
						<li>Antaragni</li>
						<li>IIT-I vs IIM-I</li>
						<li>Fluxus</li>
						<li>Festive preformances</li>
						</ul>

						<h3>Follow Dramatics club on facebook click here:
						 <a href="https://www.facebook.com/DramaticsClub.IITI/" style="color:blue;">DramaticsClub.IITI</a></h3>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="docm_club_description">
        <![CDATA[
        <h2>Designers\' Guild (DoCM)</h2>
         <p>
         The major functions of this club are:
<br>•To improve the general interest of the college junta in the visual arts such as sketching, painting, digital art, poster making, and designing in general.
<br>•To hold competitions that would serve as a platform for students of IITI to showcase their artistic talents.
<br>•To conduct workshops aimed at students interested in honing their painting, sketching and design skills.
<br>•To fulfilling the designing needs of IITI, such as magazine cover designs for our home publication Imprint and Inscription, logos and posters for various clubs, jerseys and logos for the sports team, etc.
         </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="fine_arts_club_description">
        <![CDATA[
        <h2>The Fine Arts Club (Kalakriti)</h2>
             <p>“Art is the desire of a man to express himself, to record the reactions of his personality to the world he lives in”
~Amy Lowell
The fine Arts Club is to encourage students to express their thoughts, feelings and creativity through the various visual art forms from two dimensions to three dimensions.To tap the inherent talents and potentials of the student community at all levels of life. It is a platform
 to showcase all amateurish artwork done by campus immates and to provide encouragement to them.</p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="hindi_sahitya_samiti_description">
        <![CDATA[
        <h2>Srijan- Hindi Sahitya Samiti</h2>
          <p>
          सृजन भारतीय प्रौद्योगिकी संस्थान द्वारा संचालित हिंदी साहित्य समिति है। इसका उद्देश्य छात्रों के मध्य न केवल हिंदी भाषा अपितु हिंदी साहित्य का भी विकास करना है। सृजन के द्वारा काव्य गोष्ठी, भाषण, वाद विवाद,  निबंध लेखन, हिंदी छंद कार्यशाला का आयोजन किया जाता है। सृजन द्वारा हर माह मासिक काव्य गोष्ठी का भी आयोजन किया जाता है, जिसमे संस्थान एवं बाहर के कवि भाग लेते है।  माह के आखिरी शुक्रवार को संस्थान में गीत, ग़ज़ल, कविताओं की महफ़िल जमती है । देश के प्रमुख समाचार पत्रों में काव्य गोष्ठी को जगह मिलती  रही है । वर्तमान में अकेले संस्थान से ही २० से अधिक कवि है जो गोष्ठी में नियमित रूप से काव्य पाठ करते है। सँस्थान के वार्षिक तकनीकी एवं सांस्कृतिक उत्सव फ्लक्सस (Fluxus) के उद्धघाटन में हर वर्ष काव्यांजलि कवि सम्मलेन का आयोजन किया जाता हैं।
          </p>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="avana_description">
         <![CDATA[
        <h2 style="margin:0;">Avana, IIT-Indore</h2>
						</header>
						<center><h1 style="font-size:1.5em;">An initiative by students of IIT Indore (Est. 2011) </h1>
						<h1>"Spread love everywhere you go. Let no one ever come to you without leaving happier" - Mother Teresa</h1>
						</center>
						<br>
						<h1 style="font-size:2em;">Our Activities</h1>
						<ul style="text-align:justify;">
							<li><i>Independence Day celebration (Ashrawad, Sideras)</i>: -Independence day was celebrated with the students of Ashrawad Khurd in the morning and at Sideras Orphanage in the afternoon. Prizes were distributed to the toppers of each class encouraging them to do better and better. The other kids were also given gifts.</li>
							<br><li><i>Eye donation and Eye check up camp( 16 and 18 October, 2014)</i>: - The eye screening camp was held in Silver Springs dispensary. It was organized by the Medical Team of IIT Indore and Avana in collaboration with doctors from Rajas Eye and Retina Research Centre, Indore.Also, an eye donation seminar was held by Mrs. Uma Jhawar, Director, M.K. International Eye Bank, Indore which made IIT Indore family aware about the need of eye donation, how the cornea transplant takes place and how to reach out to eye banks for such donations.</li>
							<br><li><i>Made in India Diwali</i>: -A local vendor was called to sell out the Indian made lights in order to promote the Indian made goods.</li>
							<br><li><i>Hospital Visit(Cleaning and Celebration)</i>:- We had a visit to "Chacha Nehru Child Hospital" on the eve of Deepawali for cleaning and decorating the hospital. On Deepawali, again a visit was made to the hospital for celebrating Deepawali with the children and parents present there. Each child got a gift what he/she desired for this Deepawali.</li>
							<br><li><i>Asha Vardharanjan Sewa Ashram(26 October, 2014)</i>: - A visit was made to "Asha Varadharnjan Sewa Ashram". An interaction through cultural events was made.</li>
							<br><li><i>Blood Donation(15 January,2015)</i>: - Blood Donation Camp was held at IITI hostel, Silver Springs in collaboration with Model Blood Bank, M Y Hospital.</li>
							<br><li><i>Old age home(18 January, 2015)</i>: - Again a visit was made to "Asha Varadharnjan Sewa Ashram.</li>
							<br><li>Republic day Celebration at Govt. School, Ashrawad Khurd(Detailed Description in teaching Section)</li>
							<br><li><i>Beyond The Binaries(2nd April, 2015)</i>: - Under the aegis of social FLUXUS in association with SESC, AVANA conducted a talk by Mr.Rahul Ranjan on the topic, "BEYOND THE BINARIES-Need to be talked about" emphasizing on transgender discrimination and also performed a small skit in association with ISSW, Indore.</li>
							<br><li><i>Scrap Collection</i>:- This time the scrap left over was collected from IITI hostels and sold out.</li>
							<br><li><i>Teaching at government school ashrawad khurd</i>: - Since 2 years, we were going to Govt. school,Ashrawad Khurd for uplifting the level of school. This event was conducted throughout the year.This year we involved more students of our college, especially PGs. We regularised our visits at school. We segregated kids in 2 sections according to their academic performance to teach efficiently.Our focus was to improve their English, Maths and Personality. We also selected 20 students of 5th class and prepared them for JNVV'15 entrance test. As a result of this, one of them qualified in test.Along with teaching we distributed stationery to all students and also donated dust bin for each class.On the occasion of Republic day, we taught them dance, drama, parade for a week.</li>

						</ul>


						<h3>Follow AVANA on facebook click here:
						 <a href="https://www.facebook.com/AvanaPage" style="color:blue;">AvanaPage</a></h3>

        ]]>
    </string>

    </resources>